Guide to the School of Nursing, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1921-1979; Accession 19ND-A-410
  - Series I
    - Visitors
      - Individual Visitors Folders
        - Mary O'Donnell, 1935 (Box 57, Folder 835)
        - Elinor M. Palliser, Canada, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 836)
        - Marietta Papazoph, Greece, 1947 (Box 57, Folder 837)
        - Gladys Peake, Chile, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 840)
        - Evelyn C. Pearce, England, 1947 (Box 57, Folder 841)
        - Dorothy M. Percy, 1934 (Box 57, Folder 842)
        - Miss Peters and Miss White, Japan, 1935 (Box 57, Folder 843)
        - Wilma Peterson, Canada, 1949 (Box 57, Folder 844)
        - Livia Petronia, Roumania, 1939 (Box 58, Folder 845)
        - Emily M. Pike, South Africa, 1936 (Box 58, Folder 846)
        - Marjorie Pinchbeck, Canada, 1948 (Box 58, Folder 847)
        - Stella Pines, Australia, 1930 (Box 58, Folder 848)
        - Federica Pittini, Italy, 1931 (Box 58, Folder 849)
        - K. Pohjala, Finland, 1940 (Box 58, Folder 850)
        - Irja Pohjala, Finland, 1940 (Box 58, Folder 851)
        - Gertrude Poa, China, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 852)
        - Susan M. Porzio, 1948 (Box 58, Folder 853)
        - Adela Prado, Venezuela, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 854)
        - Bertha Pullen, Brazil, 1934 (Box 58, Folder 856)
        - Mary Purcell, China, 1926 (Box 58, Folder 857)
        - Majt Rabot Sweden, 1949 (Box 58, Folder 858)
        - Lucrecia Rakela, Chile, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 859)
        - Hilda Rees, Africa, 1935 (Box 58, Folder 860)
        - Manolita Ricart, Spain, 1940 (Box 58, Folder 861)
        - M. S. Riddell, 1936 (Box 58, Folder 862)
        - Montserrat Ripol, Spain, 1933 (Box 58, Folder 863)
        - Desanka Ristovic, Yugoslavia, 1926 (Box 58, Folder 864)
        - Mary A. Ritchie, 1925 (Box 58, Folder 865)
        - Ethel E. Robinson, Canada, 1931 (Box 58, Folder 866)
        - Phyllis Robson, 1936 (Box 58, Folder 867)
        - Dr. Aristides Rodriguez, Columbia, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 868)
        - Jarmila Rousarova, Czechoslovakia, 1935 (Box 58, Folder 869)
        - Caroline Russell, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 871)
        - Anna Rydel, Poland; Marthe Patyn, Belgium, 1925 (Box 58, Folder 872)
        - Elba Saez, Chile, 1944 (Box 58, Folder 873)
        - Midori Saito, Japan, 1932 (Box 58, Folder 874)
        - Maria de San Juans, Spain, 1934 (Box 58, Folder 875)
        - Frances E. Schlossen, China, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 876)
        - Evelyn Schoen, 1938 (Box 58, Folder 877)
        - Eveline Santini, Italy, 1930 (Box 58, Folder 878)
        - Anna Schwarzenberg, Austria, 1928 (Box 58, Folder 879)
        - Mary Smik, China, 1929 (Box 58, Folder 881)
        - Jennie Browne, Ope Visalyaputr, Chamras Raemkauskula, Siam, 1934 (Box 58, Folder 883)
        - Marija Sieber, Yugoslavia, 1930 (Box 58, Folder 884)
        - Marta Sind1erova, 1934 (Box 58, Folder 885)
        - Sjohohm Filand, Miss Uhlikova Cezk, 1936 (Box 58, Folder 886)
        - Sister Mary Paul, College of St. Teresa, 1932 (Box 58, Folder 887)
        - Maria Tarr, Austria, 1926 (Box 58, Folder 888)
        - Anita Tayer, Italy, 1932 (Box 58, Folder 889)
        - Florence Taylor -D. Holland, England, 1934 (Box 58, Folder 890)
        - Marthe Thevoz, Switzerland, 1930 (Box 58, Folder 892)
        - Cecile Theys, Belgium, 1937 (Box 58, Folder 893)
        - Esther Thompson, 1931 (Box 58, Folder 894)
        - Jay S. Thompson, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 895)
        - Ravenna Tien, China, 1932 (Box 58, Folder 896)
        - Karen Tofte, Denmark, 1949 (Box 58, Folder 897)
        - Ida Topay, Hungary, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 898)
        - Grace L. Unzicker, 1926 (Box 59, Folder 899)
        - Cornelia Vassiloglou, Greece, 1931 (Box 59, Folder 900)
        - Zairea Vidal, Brazil, 1943 (Box 59, Folder 902)
        - Olga Von Lersner, Germany, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 903)
        - Lujza Wagner, Yugoslavia, 1928 (Box 59, Folder 904)
        - Elgie Wal1inger, 1926 (Box 59, Folder 905)
        - Hilda Wang, China, 1928 (Box 59, Folder 906)
        - Alice Webber, Switzerland, 1931 (Box 59, Folder 909)
        - Alexander Wacker, Hungary, 1929 (Box 59, Folder 910)
        - Ul1a Wegelius, Finland, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 911)
        - Hilde Werner, Czechoslovakia, 1934 (Box 59, Folder -912)
        - Miss Wet1esen, Norway, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 913)
        - Amanda Sloane, 1939 (Box 59, Folder 914)
        - Edith H. Smith, 1932 (Box 59, Folder 915)
        - Martha R. Smith, 1935 (Box 59, Folder 916)
        - Maria Snell, Finland, 1925 (Box 59, Folder 917)
        - Venny Snel1man, Finland, 1947 (Box 59, Folder 918)
        - Julita Sotejo, Leanor Malay, Philippines, 1941 (Box 59, Folder 920)
        - Janette Statt, 1944 (Box 59, Folder 921)
        - Lois Stearns, 1924 (Box 59, Folder 922)
        - Maria Stellar, Hungary, 1924 (Box 59, Folder 923)
        - Hedwig Sucksdorff, 1938 (Box 59, Folder 924)
        - Ching Feng Sunt, 1934 (Box 59, Folder 925)
        - Marie Sunt, 1932 (Box 59, Folder 926)
        - Aurora Sutisnut, 1938 (Box 59, Folder 927)
        - Irene Willardt, 1938 (Box 59, Folder 930)
        - Florence J. Wilson, 1936 (Box 59, Folder 931)
        - Jean Wilsont, 1942 (Box 59, Folder 932)
        - Margaret C. Winters, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 933)
        - Lulu Wolf, 1940 (Box 59, Folder 934)
        - Margaret Wong, 1932 (Box 59, Folder 935)
        - Mary Ellen Woodard, 1941 (Box 59, Folder 936)
        - Miss Wu Chin Yu, 1948 (Box 59, Folder 937)
        - Margaret Ruth Wyne, 1930 (Box 59, Folder 938)
        - Ruth Young, 1934 (Box 59, Folder 939)
        - Louise Xavier, Siam, 1930 (Box 59, Folder 940)
        - Dr. Marion Yang, 1926 (Box 59, Folder 941)
        - Sister N. Znovar, 1927 (Box 59, Folder 942)
        - Dean Mary Yost, 1934 (Box 59, Folder 943)
        - Miss Masu Yumaki, Japan, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 944)
        - Zofja Sawadzka, 1933 (Box 59, Folder 945)
        - Miss Friedericke Zehetner, 1925 (Box 59, Folder 946)
        - Miss Danica Zelenjak, 1926 (Box 59, Folder 947)
        - Dean Frances Helen Zeigler, 1942 (Box 59, Folder 948)
        - Mrs. Eloise D. Gravers, 1925 (Box 59, Folder 949)
        - Miss Tso Min Lo, China, 1940 (Box 59, Folder 950)
        - Miss Tsukokoshi, Miss Yamanato, Japan, 1928 (Box 59, Folder 951)
        - Yen Sun Tu, China, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 952)
    - Yale School of Nursing Calendar (Box 60, Folder 953)
    - The Definition of Nursing by Annie W. Goodrich (5 autographed copies) (Box 60, Folder 954)
    - 25th Anniversary of Y.S.N., (Program in Yale Journal of Biology and Medicine, March, 1949 February 5 (Box 60, Folder 955)
    - Alumnae News, 1946 (Box 60, Folder 956)
    - 25th Anniversary Exercises of Y.S.N. Programs (Box 60, Folder 957)
      - Invitation to Program (Box 60, Folder 958)
      - Tapes and transcriptions of speakers at the Y.S.N. Alumnae Day and 25th Anniversary (Box 60, Folder 959-960)
    - Reprints -American Journal of Nursing, vol 55, 1955 December (Box 60, Folder 961)
    - Reprints-Trained Nurse re: 25th Anniversary of Y.S.N., 1949 March (Box 60, Folder 962)
    - Association of Collegiate Schools of Nursing
      - Early Material: Proposal By-laws Articles Report of the President Proceedings of Conference on Proposed Association Standards Research Studies (Box 61, Folder 963)
      - Proceedings of the First Annual Meeting Proceedings of the Second Annual Meeting Proceedings of the ThirddAnnual. ,Meet ing!:c (Box 61, Folder 964)
      - Proceedings of the Fourth Annuar Meeting Proceedings of the Fifth Annual Meeting (Box 61, Folder 965)
      - Proceedings of the Sixth Annual Meeting (Box 61, Folder 966)
      - Proceedings of the Seventh Annual Meeting (Box 61, Folder 967-968)
      - Proceedings of the Eighth Annual Meeting (Box 62, Folder 969-970)
      - Proceedings of the Ninth Annual Meeting (Box 62, Folder 971-972)
      - Proceedings of the Tenth Annual Meeting (Box 62, Folder 973)
      - Proceedings of the Eleventh Annual Meeting (Box 62, Folder 974)
      - Proceedings of the Twelfth Annual Meeting; Proceedings of the Thirteenth Annual Meeting (Box 62, Folder 975)
      - Proceedings of the Fourteenth Annual Meeting (Box 63, Folder 976)
      - Proceedings of the Sixteenth Annual Meeting (Box 63, Folder 977)
      - Proceedings of the Seventeenth Annual Meeting (Box 63, Folder 978)
    - Connecticut Society for Mental Hygiene, 1947-1951 (Box 63, Folder 979)
    - Connecticut Society for Mental Hygiene, 1944-47 (Box 63, Folder 980)
    - Connecticut State League Nursing Education Board of Directors, Nov, 1946-1948 (Box 63, Folder 981)
    - Connecticut State League Nursing Education, 1943-44 (Box 63, Folder 982)
      - Administrative Committee (formerly Conn. State Supt. of Nurses Club) (Box 63, Folder 983)
    - Connecticut State Nurses Association Special Committee to work with State Mental Hospitals, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 984)
    - Connecticut State League Nursing Education Committee on University Affiliations (Box 63, Folder 985)
    - Industrial Hygiene (Box 64, Folder 986)
    - Connecticut State Advisory Council (Appointment by Governor Baldwin) (Box 64, Folder 987)
    - Yale-in-China
    - Commencement
      - 1958-60 (Box 66, Folder 996)
      - 1957-58 (Box 66, Folder 997)
      - 1955-56 (Box 66, Folder 998)
      - 1954 (Box 66, Folder 999)
      - 1951-1953 (Box 66, Folder 1000)
      - 1948-1950 (Box 66, Folder 1001)
      - 1946, 1946W, 1947, 1947W (Box 66, Folder 1002)
      - 1944, 1945 (Jan), 1945W (Box 67, Folder 1003)
      - 1942-1943 (Box 67, Folder 1004)
      - 1941 (Box 67, Folder 1005)
      - 1940 (Box 67, Folder 1006)
      - 1938-39 (Box 67, Folder 1007)
      - 1937 (Box 67, Folder 1008)
      - 1936 (Box 68, Folder 1009)
      - 1934-35 (Box 68, Folder 1010)
    - Secretary -Yale University, Mr. Lohman
      - 1938-53 (Box 68, Folder 1011)
      - 1926-37 (Box 68, Folder 1012)
    - Treasurer's Office
      - Re: affiliation fees to V.N.A. &Butler &Yale Psychiatric Clinic (Box 68, Folder 1013)
      - 1930-56 (Box 68, Folder 1014)
      - Mr. Farnam, 1936-42 (Box 69, Folder 1015)
      - Mr. Farnam, 1927-35 (Box 69, Folder 1016)
      - Mr. Ostrander, 1926-29 (Box 69, Folder 1017)
    - Records of Affiliated Students
      - Boston University (Box 69, Folder 1019-1020)
      - Butler Hospital (Box 69, Folder 1021)
      - Grace Hospital (Box 70, Folder 1022-1023)
      - Greenwich Hospital (Box 70, Folder 1024-1025)
      - Meriden Hospital (Box 70, Folder 1026-1027)
      - Middlesex Hospital (Box 71, Folder 1028-1029)
      - Norwalk Hospital (Box 71, Folder 1030-1031)
      - Norwich St. Hospital (Box 71, Folder 1032-1034)
      - New Haven Visiting Nurse Association (Box 72, Folder 1035)
    - Correspondence concerning Affiliated Students
      - Special Students -Teachers College (Box 72, Folder 1038)
      - Teacher's College Co1umbiaUniv. Dbs. Conf. (Box 72, Folder 1039)
      - University of Connecticut (Box 72, Folder 1040-1041)
      - University of Rhode Island (Box 73, Folder 1042-1043)
      - Waterbury Hospital (Box 73, Folder 1044)
      - Wm. Backus Hospital (Box 73, Folder 1045)
      - Department of Psychiatry IHR (Box 73, Folder 1046)
      - Yale Psychiatric Clinic Course for Graduate Nurses (Box 73, Folder 1047)
      - Boston University (Box 73, Folder 1048)
      - Boston University (Box 74, Folder 1049)
      - Bridgeport (Conn.) Hospital, 1939-42 (Box 74, Folder 1050)
      - Bridgeport (Conn.) Hospital, 1932-38 (Box 74, Folder 1051)
      - Butler Hospital, Providence, R.I.
        - 1947-1949-1951-1952 (Box 74, Folder 1052)
        - 1943-47 (Box 74, Folder 1053)
        - 1925-42 (Box 75, Folder 1054)
        - 1937-42 (Box 75, Folder 1055)
        - 1927-36 (Box 75, Folder 1056)
      - Grace Hospital, 1928-43 (Box 75, Folder 1057)
      - Grace Hospital, 1944-48 (Box 75, Folder 1058)
      - Temporary Graduate Course, Derby (Box 75, Folder 1059)
      - Greenwich Hospital, 1930-42 (Box 75, Folder 1060)
      - Homeopathic Hospital of Rhode Island, 1939-42 (Box 76, Folder 1061)
    - Affiliated Colleges and Universities: Folders containing General Correspondence
      - Homeopathic Hospital, Providence, R.I., 1926-38 (Box 76, Folder 1062)
      - Lawrence and-Memorial Hospital, New London, Conn., 1939-54 (Box 76, Folder 1063)
      - 'Lawrence &Memorial Hospital, New London, Conn., 1929-38 (Box 76, Folder 1064)
      - Lincoln St. Nursery School, New Haven (Box 76, Folder 1065)
      - Meriden V.N.A. Grad. students (Box 76, Folder 1966)
      - Meriden Hospital, Meriden, Conn., 1929-47 (Box 77, Folder 1067-1069)
      - Middlesex Hospital, Middletown, Conn., 1925-47 (Box 77, Folder 1070-1071)
      - Norwalk Hospital, 1930-47 (Box 77, Folder 1072-1074)
      - Radcliffe College -(Hope Ingersoll) (Box 78, Folder 1075)
      - Roger William General Hospital, 1945-48 (Box 78, Folder 1076-1077)
      - Skidmore College, 1939-42 (Box 78, Folder 1078-1079)
      - Skidmore College, 1925-38 (Box 78, Folder 1080-1081)
      - St. Mary's Hospital, Waterbury, Conn. (re. Marietta Hinman) (Box 79, Folder 1082)
      - St. Raphael's Hospital, New Haven (Box 79, Folder 1083)
      - Syracuse University (Numerous individual folders) (Box 79, Folder 1084-1085)
      - Teacher's College, Columbia University Special students (Box 79, Folder 1086-1089)
      - Tuskegee Institute (Box 80, Folder 1090-1091)
      - University of Connecticut, 1950-52 (Box 80, Folder 1092 1093)
        - School of Nursing, 1948-50 (Box 80, Folder 1092 1093)
        - School of Nursing, 1941-48 (Box 80, Folder 1094-1095)
      - University of Vermont School of Nursing (Box 81, Folder 1096)
      - Waterbury Hospital, Waterbury, Conn., 1939-47 (Box 81, Folder 1097-1098)
      - Waterbury Hospital, Waterbury, Conn. (Box 81, Folder 1099)
      - Affiliations declined (Box 81, Folder 1100)
      - Claremont General Hospital, Claremont, N.H. (Box 81, Folder 1101)
      - Childrens Hospital, Portland, Maine (Box 81, Folder 1102)
      - Cohoes Hospital, Cohoes, N.Y. (Box 81, Folder 1103)
      - Danbury Hospital, Danbury, Conn. (Box 81, Folder 1104)
      - Griffin Hospital, Derby, Conn. (Box 82, Folder 1105)
      - Hale Hospital, Haverhill, Mass. (Box 82, Folder 1106)
      - Hillcrest Hospital, Pittsfield, Mass. (Box 82, Folder 1107)
      - Litchfield County Hospital, Winsted, Conn. (Box 82, Folder 1108)
      - Mary Immaculate Hospital, Jamaica, L.I. (Box 82, Folder 1109)
      - Memorial Hospital, Pawtucket, R.I. (Box 82, Folder 1110)
      - New England Sanitarium and Hospital, Melrose, Mass. (Box 82, Folder 1111)
      - New Hampshire State Hospital, Concord, N.H. (Box 82, Folder 1112-1113)
      - North Adams Hospital, North Adams, Mass. (Box 82, Folder 1114)
      - Peck Memorial Hospital (Box 82, Folder 1115)
      - St. Luke's Hospital, Newburgh, N.Y. (Box 82, Folder 1116)
      - Trudeau Sanatorium, Trudeau, N.Y. (Box 82, Folder 1117)
      - Courses for Affiliating Students (Box 83, Folder 1119)
      - Contracts with affiliated Schools (Box 83, Folder 1120)
      - Affiliation forms and agreements (Box 83, Folder 1121)
      - Miscellaneous Data -Affiliating Schools
        - 1924-43 (Box 83, Folder 1122)
        - 1943- (Box 83, Folder 1123)
        - 1944 (Box 83, Folder 1124)
        - 1927-43 (Box 83, Folder 1125)
      - Requests for Affiliations and Affiliation Changes (Box 83, Folder 1126)
      - Misc. Memo: re: affiliation (Box 83, Folder 1127)
      - Affiliates Data, 1928-39 (Box 83, Folder 1128)
      - Increase in Affiliations Fees, 1943 (Box 83, Folder 1129)
      - Affiliation Schools --Summary of Instruction of affiliation students (Box 83, Folder 1130)
      - Affiliating Schools Conf., 1939 (Box 83, Folder 1131)
      - Replies from affiliation School re: Health Exams (Box 83, Folder 1132)
      - Affilia. Conf.
        - 1931 (Box 83, Folder 1133)
        - 1928 (Box 83, Folder 1134)
      - Affiliation fee early corresp. (Box 83, Folder 1135)
      - Sets of Charts, 1929 (Box 83, Folder 1136)
      - Nashua Hosp. Affiliates (Box 83, Folder 1137)
      - Affiliates
        - 1938-39 (Box 83, Folder 1138)
        - 1936-37 (Box 83, Folder 1139)
        - 1934-35 (Box 83, Folder 1140)
      - Auburn City Hospital, Auburn, New York (Box 84, Folder 1141)
      - 'Broad Street Hospital, Oneida, New York (Box 84, Folder 1142-1144)
      - Children's Hospital Affil.
        - A-D (Box 84, Folder 1145)
        - E-H (Box 84, Folder 1146)
        - I-P (Box 84, Folder 1147)
        - Q-S (Box 84, Folder 1148)
        - T-Z (Box 84, Folder 1149)
      - Claremont Gen. Hospital, Claremont, N.H. (Box 84, Folder 1150)
      - Cohoes Hospital, Cohoes, N.Y. (Box 84, Folder 1151)
      - Cooley -Dickinson Hospital, Northampton, Mass. (Box 84, Folder 1152)
      - Danbury Hospital, Danbury, CT.
        - A-K (Box 85, Folder 1153)
        - L-Z (Box 85, Folder 1154)
      - Ellis Hospital, Schenectady, N.Y. (Box 85, Folder 1155)
      - Litchfield County Hospital of Winchester Affil.
        - 0 (Box 86, Folder 1156)
        - D-R (Box 87, Folder 1157)
        - S-Z (Box 87, Folder 1158)
      - Hale Hospital, Haverhill, Mass. (Box 87, Folder 1159)
      - Mary Immaculate School of Nursing, Jamaica, N.Y. (Box 87, Folder 1160)
      - Melrose Hospital, Melrose, Mass. (Box 87, Folder 1161)
      - Melrose Hospital Association (Box 87, Folder 1162)
      - Memorial Hospital,Pawtucket, R.I. (Box 87, Folder 1163)
      - New Britain Gen. Hospital, N.B. CT (Box 88, Folder 1164)
      - New Britain School of Nursing
        - A-M (Box 88, Folder 1165-1168)
        - N-Z (Box 89, Folder 1169-1170)
      - N.E. Sanitarium and Hospital, Melrose, Mass. (Box 89, Folder 1171)
      - New Hampshire Mem. Hospital, Concord, N.H. (Box 89, Folder 1172-1174)
      - NH State-Hospital Affiliates
        - A-B (Box 89, Folder 1175)
        - A-B (Box 90, Folder 1176)
        - C-M (Box 90, Folder 1177-1181)
        - M-W (Box 91, Folder 1182-1186)
        - Southampton'llospita1 School of Nursing, Southampton, New York (Box 92, Folder 1187-1189)
    - Annie W. Goodrich Personal Files
      - Books -Including Gifts, etc. (Box 92, Folder 1190)
      - Brown Brothers, Harriman & Co. Cancelled Checks (Box 92, Folder 1191)
      - General (Box 92, Folder 1192)
      - Car Expense (Box 92, Folder 1193)
      - Clothing Misc. (Box 92, Folder 1194)
      - Cobalt Lodge (Box 92, Folder 1195)
      - Florists (Box 92, Folder 1196)
      - Food (Box 92, Folder 1197)
      - G. Fox, Edw. Malley, Sage Allen, Albert Steiger (Box 92, Folder 1198)
      - Handy Man -Garden, Lawn, Snow, etc. (Box 92, Folder 1199)
      - Heating Expenses (Box 92, Folder 1200)
      - Hotel Expense (Box 92, Folder 1201)
      - Household Purchases and Major Repairs (Box 92, Folder 1202)
      - AWG IncomeTax (Annie W. Goodrich) (Box 92, Folder 1203)
      - Insurance, Taxes, Dues (Box 92, Folder 1204)
      - Michael J. Lennard (Box 92, Folder 1205)
      - Magazines, Papers (Box 92, Folder 1206)
      - Telephone and Electricity (Box 92, Folder 1207)
      - AWG Personal Non-Professional (Box 93, Folder 1209)
      - Adelphi College (Box 93, Folder 1210)
      - Boston University (Box 93, Folder 1211)
      - Columbia University Teachers College Presbyteian Hospital (Box 93, Folder 1212)
      - Niagara University -Sister Eucharista (Box 93, Folder 1213)
      - Russell Sage College (Box 93, Folder 1214)
      - Skidmore College (Box 93, Folder 1215)
      - University of California (Box 93, Folder 1216)
      - University of Connecticut (Box 93, Folder 1217)
      - University of Michigan (Box 93, Folder 1218)
      - University of Pennsylvania (Box 93, Folder 1219)
      - Mlscellaneous Organizations and Institutions
        - Alabama (Box 93, Folder 1220)
        - California (Box 93, Folder 1221)
        - Colorado (Box 93, Folder 1222)
        - Connecticut (Box 93, Folder 1223)
        - D.C. (Washington) (Box 93, Folder 1224)
        - Illionois (Box 93, Folder 1225)
        - Indiana (Box 93, Folder 1226)
        - Kansas (Box 93, Folder 1227)
        - Maine (Box 93, Folder 1228)
        - Massachusetts (Box 93, Folder 1229)
        - Michigan (Box 93, Folder 1230)
        - Minnesota (Box 93, Folder 1231)
        - Missouri (Box 93, Folder 1232)
        - Montana (Box 93, Folder 1233)
        - Nebraska (Box 93, Folder 1234)
        - New Jersey (Box 93, Folder 1235)
        - New York (Box 93, Folder 1236)
        - Ohio (Box 94, Folder 1237)
        - Oregon (Box 94, Folder 1238)
        - Pennsylvania (Box 94, Folder 1239)
        - Rhode Island (Box 94, Folder 1240)
        - Tennessee (Box 94, Folder 1241)
        - Virginia (Box 94, Folder 1242)
        - Washington (Box 94, Folder 1243)
        - Wisconsin (Box 94, Folder 1244)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence
        - Africa (Box 94, Folder 1245)
        - Belgium (Box 94, Folder 1246)
        - Canada (Box 94, Folder 1247)
        - China (Box 94, Folder 1248)
        - Denmark (Box 94, Folder 1249)
        - England (Box 94, Folder 1250)
        - Finland (Box 94, Folder 1251)
        - France (Box 94, Folder 1252)
        - Germany (Box 94, Folder 1253)
        - Greece (Box 94, Folder 1254)
        - India (Box 94, Folder 1255)
        - Japan (Box 94, Folder 1256)
        - Latvia (Box 94, Folder 1257)
        - Lebanon (Box 94, Folder 1258)
        - Norway (Box 94, Folder 1259)
        - Poland (Box 94, Folder 1260)
        - South American Countries (Box 94, Folder 1261)
        - Sweden (Box 95, Folder 1262)
      - Foreign Correspondence -Misc. or Uncertain as to country (Box 95, Folder 1263)
      - International Council of Nurses (Box 95, Folder 1265)
      - Papworth lndustries, Cambridge, Summer Houses and Garden Furniture (Box 95, Folder 1266)
      - AWG Personal Family or Close Friends (Box 95, Folder 1267)
      - AWG Personal
        - Marion Goodrich and Family (Box 95, Folder 1268)
        - Katherine Hawks, Anne Hawks Vaux (Box 95, Folder 1269)
        - Markham Family, Samuel Goodrich (Box 95, Folder 1270)
        - Fred Meacham (Alfred) (Box 95, Folder 1271)
        - Health Data (Box 95, Folder 1272)
      - AWG -Yale Medal Award (Box 95, Folder 1273)
      - AWG -80th Birthday Celebration (Box 95, Folder 1274)
      - AWG Personal Financial (not household expenses) (Box 96, Folder 1275)
      - AWG Personal -Mescellaneous (Box 96, Folder 1276)
      - AWG Personal Letters (uncertain where to file) (Box 96, Folder 1277)
      - Odd and-Misplaced-Sheets (Box 96, Folder 1278)
      - Correspondence
        - A (Box 96, Folder 1279)
        - B (Box 96, Folder 1280)
        - C (Box 96, Folder 1281)
        - D (Box 96, Folder 1282)
        - E (Box 96, Folder 1283)
        - F (Box 96, Folder 1284)
        - G (Box 96, Folder 1285)
        - H (Box 96, Folder 1286)
        - I (Box 96, Folder 1287)
        - J (Box 96, Folder 1288)
        - K-L (Box 96, Folder 1289)
        - M (Box 96, Folder 1290)
        - N-O (Box 96, Folder 1291)
        - P-Q (Box 96, Folder 1292)
        - R (Box 96, Folder 1293)
        - S (Box 96, Folder 1294)
        - T (Box 96, Folder 1295)
        - U-V-W (Box 96, Folder 1296)
        - X-Y-Z (Box 96, Folder 1297)
      - Richard Olding Beard (Box 96, Folder 1298)
      - Bixler, Elizabeth S. (Box 96, Folder 1299)
      - Clippings in AWG's House File (Box 96, Folder 1300)
      - Davis Michael (Box 97, Folder 1301)
      - Dock, Lavinia (Box 97, Folder 1302)
      - Henderson, Virginia (Box 97, Folder 1303)
      - Hodgeman, Gertrude (Box 97, Folder 1304)
      - Holmes, Rev. John Haynes Connnunity Church of New lark (Box 97, Folder 1305)
      - Keller, Deane and Mrs. K., Keller, Caroline (Box 97, Folder 1306)
      - Koch, Harriet Berger -Author of AWG Biography also letters from her mother (Box 97, Folder 1307)